query:      "indigestion"
question:   "Indigestion may be caused by:"
answers:
            "Intense smells" (wrong)
            "Smoking tobacco" (correct)
            "High blood pressure" (wrong)
            "Excessive physical activity" (wrong)


query:      "dropsy disease"
question:   "Edema may be caused by:"
answers:
            "Allergies" (wrong)
            "Salmonellosis" (wrong)
            "Hormonal changes" (correct)
            "Heart problems" (wrong)


query:      "profuse sweating"
question:   "Hyperhidrosis usually affects:"
answers:
            "Back" (wrong)
            "Scalp" (wrong)
            "Cheecks" (wrong)
            "Hands and feet" (correct)


query:      "suicidal thoughts"
question:   "What is "suicidal ideation"?"
answers:
            "The active planning of a suicidal strategy" (wrong)
            "The act of encouraging someone else to commit suicide" (wrong)
            "The act of showing suicidal intentions in order to draw attention form others" (wrong)
            "The set of thoughts that a person has when considering suicide" (correct)


query:      "slow heart rate"
question:   "Which category of infants is more likely to show a slow heart rate?"
answers:
            "Premature babies" (correct)
            "Babies who are born overdue" (wrong)
            "Overweight babies" (wrong)
            "Babies with malformed bones" (wrong)


query:      "graves disease"
question:   "What is a common symptom of Grave's disease?"
answers:
            "Slow heart beats" (wrong)
            "Weight gain" (wrong)
            "Weak muscles" (correct)
            "Depression of a person's eyes" (wrong)


query:      "excessive burping"
question:   "Excessive ructus can NOT be treated by:"
answers:
            "Avoiding drinking through a straw" (wrong)
            "Taking an antacid" (wrong)
            "Eating slowly" (wrong)
            "Swallowing air" (correct)


query:      "how to lose weight"
question:   "Which of these is UNLIKELY to lead to weight loss?"
answers:
            "Avoiding beer" (wrong)
            "Avoiding fruit" (wrong)
            "A low protein diet" (correct)
            "A low carb diet" (wrong)


query:      "hair loss in women causes"
question:   "Alopecia in women is UNLIKELY to be caused by"
answers:
            "Insomnia" (correct)
            "Hormonal imbalance" (wrong)
            "Stress" (wrong)
            "Pregnancy" (wrong)


query:      "fear of heights"
question:   "Which of the following is NOT a common cause of acrophobia?"
answers:
            "Nervous reactions observed in authority figures" (wrong)
            "Depression" (correct)
            "Traumatic experiences" (wrong)
            "Conditioning" (wrong)


query:      "leg blood clot symptoms"
question:   "Which of these symptoms IS NOT associated with leg blood clots?"
answers:
            "Pain in the leg" (wrong)
            "Warmth over the affected area" (wrong)
            "Headache" (correct)
            "Change in skin color" (wrong)


query:      "can't sleep"
question:   "Which of the following is NOT a common cause of insomnia?"
answers:
            "Consuming alcoholic beverages" (wrong)
            "Consuming foods high in potassium" (correct)
            "Consuming caffeine" (wrong)
            "Worrying about falling asleep" (wrong)


query:      "hairloss"
question:   "Alopecia is most often caused by"
answers:
            "Insomnia" (wrong)
            "Severe stress" (correct)
            "Sedentary behavior" (wrong)
            "Too much excercise" (wrong)


query:      "difficulty breathing"
question:   "Which of the following is NOT a common cause of dyspnea?"
answers:
            "Asthma" (wrong)
            "Arthralgia" (correct)
            "Pneumothorax" (wrong)
            "Epiglottitis" (wrong)


query:      "body odor"
question:   "Ozochrotia is most likely to be caused by:"
answers:
            "Anti-perspirants" (wrong)
            "Triclosan" (wrong)
            "Hereditary factors / generics" (correct)
            "Regular exercise" (wrong)


query:      "salivary gland stones"
question:   "What is an effective way to remove salivary gland stones?"
answers:
            "Incision of mediastinum" (wrong)
            "Septoplasy" (wrong)
            "Sialoendoscopy" (correct)
            "salivary conducts rhinoplasty" (wrong)


query:      "excessive sweating"
question:   "Which of the following is NOT a cause of diaphoresis?"
answers:
            "Parkinson's disease" (wrong)
            "Mediastinum" (correct)
            "Intrathoracic neoplasms" (wrong)
            "Neurologic and metabolic diseases" (wrong)


query:      "nervousness"
question:   "A commonly prescribed drug for attenuate nervousness is:"
answers:
            "Taxol" (wrong)
            "Xalatan" (wrong)
            "Acyclovir" (wrong)
            "Buspirone" (correct)


query:      "sunlight causing hives"
question:   "What makes solar urticaria different from a sunburn?"
answers:
            "It requires a lot longer exposure period to sunlight that the time necessary to get a sunburn" (wrong)
            "It occurs within minutes after being exposed to sunlight" (correct)
            "The burning feeling caused by solar urticaria lasts a lot longer that the one caused by sunburn" (wrong)
            "Unlike sunburn, it affects the whole body at once instead of affecting only the parts that are exposed to sunlight." (wrong)


query:      "foods to avoid with acid reflux"
question:   "Which of these foods is UNLIKELY to cause gastroesophageal reflux?"
answers:
            "low-fat foods" (correct)
            "foods containing tomatos" (wrong)
            "coffee" (wrong)
            "french fries" (wrong)


query:      "trouble swallowing when eating"
question:   "Which one of these problems can cause issue in swallowing?"
answers:
            "Hypophosphatasia" (wrong)
            "Achalasia" (correct)
            "Esophageal disease" (wrong)
            "Bone spur" (wrong)


query:      "how to stop a nosebleed"
question:   "Which of the following actions may help stopping an epistaxis?"
answers:
            "Lean flat" (wrong)
            "Blow nose" (wrong)
            "Pinch the nose every 5 minutes" (correct)
            "Put head between legs" (wrong)


query:      "hives"
question:   "Urticaria is often caused by"
answers:
            "Allergic reactions" (correct)
            "Weight gain" (wrong)
            "Depression" (wrong)
            "Consuming caffeine" (wrong)


query:      "common cold symptoms"
question:   "Which of the following is NOT a common symptom of nasopharyngitis?"
answers:
            "High fever" (correct)
            "Nasal stuffiness" (wrong)
            "Fatigue" (wrong)
            "Sore throat" (wrong)


query:      "stress incontinence"
question:   "What can cause stress incontinence?"
answers:
            "Childbirth" (correct)
            "Psychological condition" (wrong)
            "High blood pressure" (wrong)
            "Genetic predisposition" (wrong)


query:      "sweating sickness"
question:   "What is "focal hyperhidrosis"?"
answers:
            "Excessive sweating that occurs when trying to focus" (wrong)
            "Lack of sweating in stressful situations" (wrong)
            "Excessive sweating in specific body regions" (correct)
            "Lack of sweating in specific body regions" (wrong)


query:      "bloated stomach"
question:   "Which of the following actions can lead to abdominal bloating?"
answers:
            "Pollen allergies" (wrong)
            "Consuming diet or sugar-free foods" (correct)
            "Sore throat" (wrong)
            "Consuming fruits" (wrong)


query:      "blood clot"
question:   "What is the medical term for a blood clot in a vein?"
answers:
            "Venous thrombosis" (correct)
            "Venous embolus" (wrong)
            "Arterial embolism" (wrong)
            "Arterial thrombi" (wrong)


query:      "sweet sweat"
question:   "What is one of the possible side effects when using Sweet Sweat?"
answers:
            "It may cause circulation problems in stomach or upper thighs" (wrong)
            "It may cause an uptick in the thermogenic process" (correct)
            "It may cause irritations on the skin" (wrong)
            "It may cause an increase in blood pressure" (wrong)


query:      "kidney failure symptoms"
question:   "Which of these symptoms is NOT associated with renal insufficiency"
answers:
            "Shortness of breath" (correct)
            "Weight Loss" (wrong)
            "Itching" (wrong)
            "High potassium concentration in blood" (wrong)


query:      "trouble swallowing"
question:   "Which of these tests is commonly used to detect a swallowing problem?"
answers:
            "Ophthalmoscopy" (wrong)
            "Nasal endoscopy" (wrong)
            "Cineradiography" (correct)
            "Laryngoscopy" (wrong)


query:      "heat stroke"
question:   "Which of the following is NOT a common symptom of heat exhaustion?"
answers:
            "Nausea" (wrong)
            "Slow pulse" (correct)
            "Dry skin" (wrong)
            "Hot skin" (wrong)


query:      "spontaneous abortion"
question:   "Which disease DOES NOT statistically increase the rate of miscarriage?"
answers:
            "Autoimmune disease" (wrong)
            "Glucagonoma" (correct)
            "Diabetes mellitus" (wrong)
            "Hypothyroidism" (wrong)


query:      "foods cause gout"
question:   "Gout is unlikely to be caused by"
answers:
            "Eating smaller meals throughout the day instead of eating three large meals" (correct)
            "Broccoli" (wrong)
            "Dairy foods" (wrong)
            "Brussel sprouts" (wrong)


query:      "bloody stools in adults"
question:   "Which of the following is unlikely to cause hematochezia in adults?"
answers:
            "Salmonellosis" (wrong)
            "Food allergies" (correct)
            "Upper GI bleeding" (wrong)
            "Hemmorrhoids" (wrong)


query:      "back problems"
question:   "Back pain is usually caused by injury to the:"
answers:
            "Thoracic spine" (wrong)
            "Spinal cord" (wrong)
            "None of the above" (correct)
            "Cervical spine" (wrong)


query:      "indigestion symptoms"
question:   "A common symptom of dyspepsia is:"
answers:
            "Dysphagia" (wrong)
            "Blunt trauma" (wrong)
            "Hemiplegia" (wrong)
            "Belching" (correct)


query:      "shaking hands"
question:   "What are rest tremors?"
answers:
            "Involuntary movement that happen when the body is at rest" (correct)
            "The inability of keeping hands in a resting position." (wrong)
            "an increase in shakiness when the patient tries to rest" (wrong)
            "hands movements when the temperature is very low" (wrong)


query:      "ringing ears"
question:   "What is objective tinnitus?"
answers:
            "An actual sound coming from the ear of a person" (correct)
            " A symptom of ringing ears" (wrong)
            "A treatment for ringing ears" (wrong)
            "A perceived sound from a patient caused by exposure to excessive sounds" (wrong)


query:      "memory loss"
question:   "Which of the following is a type of amnesia?"
answers:
            "Crossexposed amnesia" (wrong)
            "Retrograde amnesia" (correct)
            "Fragmented amnesia" (wrong)
            "Parallel amnesia" (wrong)


query:      "nosebleed"
question:   "Which of these conditions is NOT a predisposition factor for nosebleed?"
answers:
            "Sinus infection" (wrong)
            "Diabetes" (correct)
            "Allergies" (wrong)
            "Hypertension" (wrong)


query:      "brown vaginal discharge"
question:   "Brown mucopurulent discharge can be caused by:"
answers:
            "Trichomoniasis" (wrong)
            "Endometrial cancer" (correct)
            "Yeast infection" (wrong)
            "Influenza" (wrong)


query:      "memory loss in women"
question:   "Memory impairment is most commonly caused by:"
answers:
            "Unbalanced diet" (wrong)
            "Sudden motion" (wrong)
            "High blood pressure" (wrong)
            "Depression" (correct)


query:      "pressure ulcers"
question:   "What is the most common cause for pressure ulcers?"
answers:
            "Lack of hygiene" (wrong)
            "Pysical injury" (wrong)
            "Limited ability to move" (correct)
            "Skin rushes" (wrong)


query:      "acid reflux symptoms"
question:   "Which of these symptoms is a symptom of GERD?"
answers:
            "feeling of having food stuck in one's throat" (correct)
            "restlessness" (wrong)
            "dry eyes" (wrong)
            "feelings of discontent" (wrong)


query:      "what causes hair loss in women"
question:   "What is alopecia areata?"
answers:
            "Loss of hair on all the body" (wrong)
            "Loss of hair in some spots on the body" (correct)
            "A risk factor for hair loss" (wrong)
            "Treatment for loss of hair" (wrong)


query:      "erectile dysfunction remedies"
question:   "Impotentia coeundi is commonly caused by:"
answers:
            "Pollen allergies" (wrong)
            "Anti-depressants" (correct)
            "Insomnia" (wrong)
            "Lack of movement" (wrong)


query:      "tooth ache"
question:   "Which part of the mouth does "gum disease" affect?"
answers:
            "Periodontium" (correct)
            "Salivary glands" (wrong)
            "Enamel" (wrong)
            "Dentin" (wrong)


query:      "acid reflux"
question:   "Which of these conditions causes symptoms similar to those caused by acid reflux disease?"
answers:
            "Asthma, GORD, and dysphagia" (wrong)
            "GERD and heartburn" (wrong)
            "GERD, heartburn, and asthma" (correct)
            "GERD, GORD, and heartburn" (wrong)


query:      "double vision causes"
question:   "Which of the following is NOT a common cause of diplopia?"
answers:
            "Cataracts" (wrong)
            "Corneal scars" (wrong)
            "Dryness" (wrong)
            "Trichomoniasis" (correct)
